tvacreditunion.com 2019-07-17

# FACTS

                    What does Knoxville TVA Employees Credit Union do with
FACTS               your personal information?                                                                                 Rev 12/2014
Why?                Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to
                    limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal
                    information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?               The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. The
                    information can include:
                    • Social Security number and income; • Account balances and payment history; • Credit history and credit scores
                    When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
                    TVA Employees Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                              Does Knoxville TVA Employees
Reasons we can share your personal information                     Credit Union share?                    Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes— such as to
process your transactions, maintain your account(s),                          Yes                                      No
respond to court orders and legal investigations, or
report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—                                                   Yes                                      No
and services to you
                                                                              Yes                                      No
                                                  —                           No                                 We don’t share
information about your transactions and experiences
                                                  —                           No                                 We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
                                                                              No                                 We don’t share
Questions?          Call 865-544-5400 or 800-467-5427 or go to tvacreditunion.com.
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?            Knoxville TVA Employees Credit Union
What we do
How does Knoxville TVA Employees         To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security
Credit Union protect my personal         measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and
information?
How does Knoxville TVA Employees         We collect your personal information, for example when you
Credit Union collect my personal         • open an account or deposit money
information?                             • pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                         • use your credit or debit card
                                         We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?           Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                         •
                                         •
                                         •
                                         State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
                                         companies.
                                         •
                                         •
Joint marketing
                                         • Insurance providers and investment services.
